# **Scott Nnaghor**

0736 866 0611 Barking, London

scottmike275@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/scott-nnaghor-75128a11b/ https://www.scottnnaghor.com/

# Personal Profile

I am a Graduate of Middlesex University and Roehampton University, where I achieved First Class Honours in Bsc Information Technology and Business Information Systems and Merit Honours in Masters of Computer Science. I have commercial experience as a Software Engineer and Web Developer and working knowledge of developing web applications for clients and would consider myself highly skilled in strategic product development and focus on developing and executing software applications.

# **Education**

Roehampton University, 2020-2021

**Msc in Computing** 

Merit

# Notable topics of:

Software Development 1, Software Development 2, Cyber security, Computing and society, Database design, Computing Systems.

## Middlesex University, 2019-2020

Bsc in Computer Science (Hons) in Information Technology & Business Information Systems First Class Honours

## Notable topics of:

Business Intelligence, Strategic Information Systems Management – Enterprise Project, User Experience Design, Undergraduate Individual Project – Investigating the development of a Web platform for an enhanced customer shopping experience

Aptech Computer Education, 2015-2018 Lagos, Nigeria

Diploma in Advance Diploma in Software Engineering

## Relevant Skills and Competencies -

PHP, Python, NodeJS, Flutter, React Native, PHP CodeIgniter, WordPress, Wix, Java, SQL

# Relevant Experience

Web Developer, Spiela, London, United Kingdom March 2020 – February 2022

- I built the web application and enhanced the layout and functionality from the previous version.
- I improved the web application to provide better user experience and being able to reach a larger audience and also creating the platform for an online community for people to discuss key issues in the society.
- Achievement: Revamped the Web platform which increased the user experience and engagement.
- URL https://spiela.co.uk

Web Developer (Intern), IAmTheCode, London, United Kingdom,

## December 2020 - January 2021

- I handled the project called Accur8 Africa, and upgraded the website by integrating features that relate to Digital Marketing, Cyber Security and Artificial Intelligence.
- Achievement: The web platform improved from its previous state.

Web Developer (Intern), Future Care, London, United Kingdom, November 2019 - Jan 2020

- Managed the company CRM (Customer relationship Management) system using HubSpot.
- I raised efficiency and productivity immensely in the number of sales from prospects.
- Enhanced to give clients a richer experience when accessing the website.
- Achievement: Developed Futurecare and Falls predict using WordPress as project.
- URL http://www.fallspredict.com

Software Developer, Infinity Genius, Lagos, Nigeria, Jan 2018 - June 2019

- Contributed in developing a web platform for the music artiste in reaching a larger audience.
- Built a feature in the web platform to allow users sample songs and buy the full album.
- Negotiated contracts with the vendors for payment gateway system, which further reduced the cost, while raising more profit to the artiste through the use of the e-wallet feature in the website.
- Contributed in developing a web platform for a school agent.
- Increased the experience, leading to increased profitability.
- Achievement: Developed an E-wallet application for users to make payment on the web platform and creating a Content Management System (CMS) to give the client full control on the websitelayout.

## **Web Projects**

#### Web Developer, Hotel App

- I developed a hotel platform where customers can go and check for available rooms, view the rooms that are available in a calendar and be able to book the room.
- The platform also connects to PayPal payment API to access payment
- Achievement: A full working platform that consists of a restaurant, admin and user portal
- URL https://scottnnaghor.com/hotel/home

## Web Developer, E-commerce App

- I built an eCommerce application using PHP for my Undergraduate degree project about how to improve the shopping experience of online shoppers.
- The platform had an inbuilt digital wallet and membership feature to ease the shopping experience of online customers.
- The platform also connects to PayPal payment API to access payment
- Achievement: Achieved a Distinction on my Dissertation
- URL https://scottnnaghor.com/ecommerce/home

## Web Developer, Fast Food App

- The platform has a delivery fast food application that can allow users to schedule when they want their meals to be delivered to them.
- The platform also connects to a Stripe Payment gateway to access payment
- Achievement: An optimized web application that has a staff and user's section.
- URL https://scottnnaghor.com/fastfood/home

## Flutter Developer, EatandMore

- I worked on the Fast-food mobile app which delivers various foods to their customers in the United Kingdom
- Achievement: The layout of the application was improved and was able to publish on the Google Play Store.
- Google Play Store: EatandMore

#### Web Designer, Makbess

- This platform is built for a client who is in the Film industry to share and advertise the various films and trailers that the client has worked on.
- Achievement: The web platform has a video player feature to give user's the access to watch some trailers of the client films.
- URL: https://makbess.com

# Web Developer, Royal Ethon

# Academy

- This project is for a school platform where students and teachers can access their online portals and be able to track their grades, attendance, training, classes and other academic activities on their dashboard.
- The admin of the platform could monitor all the activities in the school from business to academic and the progress of the staff.
- Achievement: The web platform made it easier for students to access their grades and teachers to monitor their students' progress.
- URL: https://royalethonacademy.com

# Web Developer,

# MaidinChelsea Cleaning

- This platform is built to equip the owner to provide their cleaning services to their clients in South West London.
- The admin of the platform could monitor all the activities in the platform and can make changes which are similar to a Content Management System.
- Achievement: The website provided the owner with a platform to market their services and business.
- URL: https://maidinchelseacleaning.com

# **References Available Upon Request**